<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide App</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="miami_city_description">
        Miami is an international city at Floridas southeastern tip. Its Cuban influence is
        reflected in the cafes and cigar shops that line Calle Ocho in Little Havana. On barrier
        islands across the turquoise waters of Biscayne Bay is Miami Beach, home to South Beach.
        This glamorous neighborhood is famed for its colorful art deco buildings, white sand,
        surfside hotels and trendsetting nightclubs.
    </string>
    <string name="vizcaya_description">The Vizcaya Museum and Gardens, previously known as Villa
        Vizcaya, is the former villa and estate of businessman James Deering, of the Deering
        McCormick-International Harvester fortune, on Biscayne Bay in the present day Coconut
        Grove neighborhood of Miami, Florida. The early 20th century Vizcaya estate also includes:
        extensive Italian Renaissance gardens; native woodland landscape; and a historic village
        outbuildings compound. The landscape and architecture were influenced by Veneto and Tuscan
        Italian Renaissance models and designed in the Mediterranean Revival architecture style,
        with Baroque elements. Paul Chalfin was the design director. Miami-Dade County
        now owns the Vizcaya property, as the Vizcaya Museum and Gardens, which is open to the
        public. The location is served by the Vizcaya Station of the Miami Metrorail.</string>
    <string name="lincoln_road_description">Lincoln Road Mall is a pedestrian road running east-west
        parallel between 16th Street and 17th Street in Miami Beach, Florida, United States. Once
        completely open to vehicular traffic, it now hosts a pedestrian mall replete with shops,
        restaurants, galleries, and other businesses between Washington Avenue with a traffic
        accessible street extending east to the Atlantic Ocean and west to Alton Road with a traffic
        accessible street extending to Biscayne Bay.</string>
    <string name="coral_castle_description">Coral Castle is an oolite limestone structure created
        by the Latvian American eccentric Edward Leedskalnin (1887–1951). It is located in Leisure
        City, Florida, in Miami-Dade County at the intersection of South Dixie Highway (U.S. 1) and
        SW 157th Avenue. The structure comprises numerous megalithic stones, mostly limestone formed
        from coral, each weighing several tons. It is currently a privately operated tourist
        attraction. Coral Castle is noted for legends surrounding its creation that claim it was
        built single-handedly by Leedskalnin using reverse magnetism or supernatural abilities to
        move and carve numerous stones weighing many tons</string>
    <string name="venetian_pool_description">
        Venetian Pool is a historic U.S. public swimming pool located in Coral Gables, Florida.
        Completed in 1924, it was designed by Phineas Paist with Denman Fink.The pool occupies a
        shallow quarry displacing some 820,000 US gallons (3,100 m3) of fresh water daily from
        artesian wells, making it the largest freshwater pool in the United States.The pool ranges
        in depth from four feet to depths of over eight feet near the grand waterfall, with a
        two-foot kiddy pool near the lifeguard station; the station is atop a bridge leading out to
        an island with two full size palm trees on it. A grotto, where natural water-filled caves
        stretch back over twelve feet into the hillside, is located across the pool from the island.
        There is a sandy sunning area for sunbathers and a café area that is commonly used for
        weddings and receptions. A walking path surrounds the whole complex. The pool received a
        massive historical restoration in 1989. The pool has recently had another major
        renovation which took eight months to complete (September 8, 2008 - April 30, 2009) and
        has since re-opened to the public again.</string>

    <string name="vizcaya_address">\n ADDRESS: \n 3251 S Miami Ave, Miami, FL 33129</string>
    <string name="lincoln_road_address">\n ADDRESS: \n Lincoln Rd, Miami Beach, FL 33139</string>
    <string name="coral_castle_address">\n ADDRESS: \n 28655 S Dixie Hwy, Homestead, FL 33033</string>
    <string name="venetian_pool_address">\n ADDRESS: \n 2701 De Soto Blvd, Coral Gables, FL 33134</string>

    <string name="vizcaya_hours">\n HOURS OF OPERATION: \n April 2017 – November 2017 \n \n
        August 21, 2017 – September 10, 2017 \n • Monday – Friday: 11:00 a.m. – 5:30 p.m. \n
        • Saturday – Sunday: 10:00 a.m. – 4:30 p.m. \n \n September 12, 2017 – October 29, 2017 \n
        • Tuesday – Friday: 11:00 a.m. – 5:30 p.m. \n • Saturday – Sunday: 10:00 a.m. – 4:30 p.m. \n \n
        October 31, 2017 – November 30, 2017 \n • Tuesday – Sunday: 10:00 a.m. – 4:30 p.m. \n </string>
    <string name="lincoln_road_hours"> \n HOURS OF OPERATION: \n \n • Monday - Sunday 10:00 a.m. - 11:00 p.m.</string>
    <string name="coral_castle_hours"> \n HOURS OF OPERATION: \n \n • Sunday - Thursday 9:00 a.m. - 5:00 p.m.
        \n • Friday - Saturday 9:00 a.m. - 7:00 p.m. </string>
    <string name="venetian_pool_hours"> \n HOURS OF OPERATION: \n \n • Monday - Sunday 10:00 a/m/ - 4:30 p.m.</string>
    <string name="information">Information</string>
    <string name="hours_directions"><![CDATA[Hours & Directions]]></string>
    <string name="vizcaya_name">Vizcaya Museum and Gardens</string>
    <string name="lincoln_road_name">Lincoln Road</string>
    <string name="coral_castle_name">Coral Castle</string>
    <string name="venetian_pool_name">Venetian Pool</string>
    <string name="miami_name">Miami</string>
    <string name="description">description</string>
    <string name="title">title</string>
    <string name="address">address</string>
    <string name="hours">hours</string>
</resources>
